{"tossups": [{"question": "With the help of his uncle Charles W. Smith, this man served as a legal advisor to Jay Gould. This one-time railroad manager and Indiana senator was the subject of a decision made by E.T. Barnette that was intended to ease the process of receiving aid from the federal government. This man was on the winning ticket of an electoral defeat for Alton Parker, but was accused of being a \u201cmachine politician\u201d by the president he served under. This opponent of the Square Deal had an Alaska city named after him. For the point, name this Vice President under Theodore Roosevelt.", "answer": "Charles W(arren) <b><u>Fairbanks</u></b>", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "While hoping to enlist in the Army as an aviator during the First World War, this composer wrote <em>Trois Chansons</em>, based on 16th century French pieces. Sergei Diaghilev of Ballet Russes commissioned this composer to create <em>La Valse</em>, a tribute to the waltz. This composer adapted six pieces from Isaac Alb\u00e9niz's set of piano pieces, <em>Iberia</em>, into the orchestral piece <em>Bolero</em>. For the point, name this French composer of <em>Daphnis et Chlo\u00e9</em> and <em>Gaspard de la nuit</em>.", "answer": "Maurice <b><u>Ravel</u></b> (or Joseph Maurice <b><u>Ravel</u></b>)", "metadata": "Fine Arts - Auditory Fine Arts"}, {"question": "This man's successor Yun Posun ruled as a figurehead controlled by the Supreme Council for National Reconstruction. This man, who went into exile to Hawaii following the killing of 180 students in the April Revolution, subdued the Jeju Island uprising after their Worker's Party agitated for autonomy. This Prime Minister abandoned his national capital for Busan following a 1950 invasion, later recovered after victories at Osan and Inchon. For the point, name this first Prime Minister of independent South Korea.", "answer": "<b><u>Rhee</u></b> Syngman (or Syngman <b><u>Rhee</u></b>; prompt on \"Syngman\")", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "The first Admirals Club was opened in this location, whose organizer originally tried to arrange for police to escort limousines from a venue named for Floyd Bennett. This facility sometimes has the acronym \u201cUSS\u201d informally appended before it in reference to the water that surrounds its runways. A press conference that inspired the creation of this venue was given after its namesake was taken to Newark instead of the city he led. For the point, name this airport in Queens named for a mayor of New York.", "answer": "<b><u>LaGuardia</u></b> Airport (accept K<b><u>LGA</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "Following Yuan Shao's defeat at Guandu, this man led a force against Jing Province, overthrowing Liu Biao. After his victory at the Battle of Tong Pass, this man sent Zhu [[SHU]] Ling and Xiahou [[shee-ah-HOH]] Yuan to fight against the Di tribes. This man's campaign to restore the lands of the Eastern Han was halted at the Battle of Red Cliffs, where he was defeated by Liu Bei and Sun Quan [[CHOO-wan]]. For the point, name this Three Kingdoms era warlord, founder of the state of Wei.", "answer": "<b><u>Cao Cao</u></b> (accept Cao <b><u>Mengde</u></b>; prompt on <b><u>Cao</u></b> alone)", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "The best explanation for the deaths of this man and his sons, Paralus and Xanthippus [[zan-THIP-uss], was determined to be typhus at a 1999 epidemiology conference. According to Plutarch, this man's fathering of a namesake son with Aspasia [[ah-SPAY-shah]] led to accusations of corruption. This man developed a grand strategy that involved not facing the army of Sparta, but instead foiling their plan for victory. For the point, name this Athenian statesman of the \"Golden Age\" who commissioned the Parthenon.", "answer": "<b><u>Pericles</u></b>", "metadata": "History - Ancient History"}, {"question": "The first Margrave of this city was the ancestor of members of the Frankish Obertenghi family. 46 percent of this city\u2019s population is thought to have died in a 1629-1631 plague. One of this city's rulers was defeated at Novara by Louis XII [[the twelfth]]. This city was led by a man nicknamed \u201cthe Moor,\u201d or \u201cil Moro,\u201d who patronized da Vinci\u2019s <em>The Last Supper</em>. The Sforza family ruled over this city, which once was capital of the Western Roman Empire. For the point, name this capital of Lombardy.", "answer": "<b><u>Milan</u></b> (accept <b><u>Milano</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {"question": "On the edges of late-medieval English texts, these animals are often seen in combat with knights, possibly in reference to the treacherous Gothic people. The Swabian town of Guttenstein became the center for selling these animals in the early 20th century, sending over four million of these animals to France per year. A predatory type of these animals named <em>Murax</em> are used to create Tyrian Purple, the color associated with Roman emperors. For the point, name these gastropods used for the dish <em>escargot</em>.", "answer": "<b><u>Snail</u></b> (accept <b><u>Slug</u></b>; accept <b><u>Murax</u></b> or <b><u>Escargot</u></b> before mentioned)", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {"question": "During this conflict, the 11th Lord Lovat was nicknamed \u201cthe Fox\u201d after switching his allegiance. One leader during this conflict called for the dispersal of troops at Ruthven Barracks until the arrival of French reinforcements. Though he won an early battle at Prestonpans, this conflict was decided by a defeat outside Inverness for the \u201cYoung Chevalier.\u201d The Duke of Cumberland earned the nickname \"Butcher\" for his behavior after putting this rebellion down at the Battle of Culloden. For the point, what pro-Stuart rebellion was led by Bonnie Prince Charlie?", "answer": "<b><u>Jacobite</u></b> Rising of <b><u>1745</u></b> (accept the <b><u>Forty-Five</u></b> Rebellion; accept <b><u>Bliadhna</u></b> <b><u>The\u00e0rlaich</u></b>; accept The <b><u>Year of Charles</u></b>; prompt on \"Jacobite\" Rising alone)", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {"question": "During this event, Quaker Edwin Coppock killed Mayor Fontaine Beckham and freed his five slaves. Much of this event\u2019s planning occurred in the Kennedy farmhouse, and this event\u2019s leader sent an invitation to Frederick Douglass to join the armed cohorts. Colonel Robert E. Lee was assigned to defeat this attack against a certain arsenal. For the point, name this attempt by John Brown to start a slave revolt in Virginia.", "answer": "John Brown's raid on the U.S. arsenal at <b><u>Harpers Ferry</u></b>", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "Catholic novelist Ayako Sono gave refuge to this politician after he fled his nation, and while there, his attempted resignation by fax machine was rejected by the National Congress. This politician paraded Maoist insurgent Abimael [[ah-BEE-mah-EL]] Guzman in a cartoonesque prison outfit and cage in his national capital. This man's daughter, Keiko, made a failed bid to win the 2021 federal election, narrowly losing to union leader Pedro Castillo. For the point, name this right-wing president of Peru who defeated the Shining Path insurgency.", "answer": "Alberto <b><u>Fujimori</u></b> (or Alberto Kenya <b><u>Fujimori</u></b> Inomoto)", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "This man failed to decisively influence the Skirmish at Glendale during the larger Battle of the Seven Pines after failing to ford White Oak Swamp. On the eve of secession, this man organized a raid on the B & O Railroad by blowing up a bridge in Martinsburg in his home state of West Virginia. This general, who died from wounds received from friendly fire, earned his nickname after holding firm during the Battle of Bull Run. For the point, name this tactically brilliant Confederate general who fell at the Battle of Chancellorsville.", "answer": "Thomas \u201cStonewall\u201d <b><u>Jackson</u></b> (or Thomas Jonathan \"Stonewall\" <b><u>Jackson</u></b>", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "Babur possibly imported this geophyte into India from Afghanistan, though its earliest cultivation was likely in 10th century Persia. An era of 18th century Ottoman history with this name is known for its relative peace, due to vizier's Damat Ibrahim's love for this good. Beginning in the Netherlands during the Dutch Golden Age, forty of these flowers sold for 100,000 <em>guilders</em>. The first mass speculative bubble in history occurred over, for the point, what plant during a namesake period of \"Mania\" in 17th century Europe?", "answer": "<b><u>Tulip</u></b> (accept <b><u>Tulip</u></b> Era; accept <b><u>Tulip</u></b> Mania)", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "A duty levied on this good by the administration of William Pitt led ambassador John Adams to say the tariff \"sacrifices the general interest of the nation to the private interests of a few individuals.\" The final engagement of the Civil War occurred when the USS <em>Shenandoah</em> sank Union ships in this industry off the Aleutian islands. The city of Nantucket served as a hub of this industry in the 17th and 18th century due to its proximity to the open ocean. For the point, name this industry centered around hunting a marine mammal with Baleen and Sperm species.", "answer": "<b><u>Whaling</u></b> (accept answers involving catching or hunting <b><u>Whale</u></b>s; accept the collecting of <b><u>Whale Oil</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "The Department of the Treasury was required to inspect these vehicles. Tom Lee Park in Memphis is named for a man who rescued people from these vehicles. Many of these vehicles like the <em>Annie Faxon</em> were destroyed because of the failure of fusible plugs. Robert Fulton and Robert Livingston owned one of these vehicles on the Hudson called the <em>Clermont</em>. Mark Twain's <em>Life on the Mississippi</em> documents, for the point, what type of boat?", "answer": "<b><u>Steam</u></b>boat(s) (or <b><u>Steamer</u></b>s; accept Paddle <b><u>Steamer</u></b>; accept Screw <b><u>Steamer</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "Every Pentacost, people would sing songs that Francois-Joseph Gossec composed at the Champ de Mars for a festival this man invented. This man forced the arrest of Theresa Cabarrus and Cecile Renault hid two penknives in an attempt to kill him. This leader declared an end of the slave trade in the Declaration of the Rights of the Man and of the Citizen. Together with Louis de Saint-Just, this man radicalized the Committee of Public Safety. For the point, name this Jacobin politician who led the Reign of Terror during the French Revolution.", "answer": "Maximilien <b><u>Robespierre</u></b> (or Maximilien Fran\u00e7ois Marie Isidore de <b><u>Robespierre</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {"question": "Two young royals were killed in this city after being invited for the \u201cBlack Dinner.\u201d In this city, the hanging of a convicted smuggler led to a mob disturbance which resulted in the killing of John Porteous. The aforementioned hanging took place in the Grassmarket section of this city, which contains St. Giles\u2019 Cathedral. This city\u2019s Royal Mile connects to the Holyrood Palace, which was once inhabited by the wife of Lord Darnley. John Knox was ordained in this city, once ruled by Mary Stuart. For the point, name this capital city of Scotland.", "answer": "<b><u>Edinburgh</u></b>", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {"question": "Oguz-Bashi mountain was renamed for this man, who left Taoiseach [[TEE-shuk]] Albert Reynolds embarrassed after he appeared drunk at Shannon Airport. In a strange incident in Stockholm, this man compared Swedish meatballs to Bjorn Borg's face, and he was once found drunk in Washington D.C., trying to buy pizza in his underwear. Oleg Soskovets helped this man develop a strategy to win re-election in 1996. This man faced the Chechen War and returned the KAL 007 black box. For the point, name this first president of the Russian Federation, preceding Vladimir Putin.", "answer": "Boris <b><u>Yeltsin</u></b> (or Boris Nikolayevich <b><u>Yeltsin</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {"question": "This man co-authored a book with Alexis Carrel that focuses on keeping organs intact outside the body, and he was married to a daughter of Calvin Coolidge\u2019s Ambassador to Mexico, Dwight Morrow. This man was the youngest and first man to appear on the cover of TIME magazine. Bruno Hauptmann demanded a ransom from this spokesman for the America First Committee after kidnapping his son. For the point, what aviator made history with the first solo transatlantic flight in his plane, <em>The Spirit of St. Louis</em>?", "answer": "Charles <b><u>Lindbergh</u></b> (or Charles Augustus <b><u>Lindbergh</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "A major rebel leader in this country is often referred to as Penguin. This country\u2019s UDD, which are alternatively called the Red Shirts, opposed a coup in 2006 that toppled a telecommunications magnate who led it. The People\u2019s Alliance of Democracy was founded in this country, where prison sentences of up to fifteen years can be leveled upon those who insult its monarch. In 2016, the tenth Chakri monarch, Rama X [[\"the tenth\"]], took the throne of this country. For the point, name this southeast Asian country, the only one to ally with Japan during World War Two.", "answer": "Kingdom of <b><u>Thai</u></b>land (accept Ratcha-anachak <b><u>Thai</u></b>; prompt on \"Siam\")", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "A soldier who founded a major party in this country gained the nickname \u201cBlowtorch Bob\u201d for his use of blowtorches in interrogations. Over 30,000 people were killed in this country during La Matanza. The Chapultepec Peace Accords ended a twelve-year civil war in this country, which contains the ARENA and FMLN parties. In 1970, riots during a World Cup qualifier led to the Soccer War between this country and Honduras. For the point, name this Central American country east of Guatemala.", "answer": "Republic of <b><u>El Salvador</u></b> (accept Rep\u00fablica de <b><u>El Salvador</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "William Henry Hunt was appointed Secretary of the Navy by this president, who called for the abandonment of the Clayton-Bulwer Treaty. Morrison Waite was made Chief Justice under this president, who appointed William Robertson as Collector of the Port of New York. During an earlier man\u2019s presidency, this man refused ten shares offered by Oakes Ames during the Credit Mobilier Scandal. The death of this man prompted the passage of the Pendleton Civil Service Act under his successor. For the point, name this president who was assassinated in 1881 by Charles Guiteau.", "answer": "James A(bram) <b><u>Garfield</u></b>", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "At the Faculty of Cologne, Heinrich Kramer wrote a book about these people, <em>Malleus Maleficarum</em> [[mah-leh-FEE-cah-RUM]] after being rebuffed by peasant woman Helena Scheuberin [[SHOO-bare-in]]. Cotton Mather defended his actions during 1692 colonial trials concerning these people in his pamphlet, <em>Wonders of the Invisible World</em>. For the point, name these supposed supernatural people who were executed in various manners during trials in Salem, Massachusetts.", "answer": "<b><u>Witch</u></b> (accept male equivalents like <b><u>Warlock</u></b> or <b><u>Wizard</u></b>; accept more general answers like <b><u>Magician</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "While taking a break from this activity in a Middle English poem, a peasant named Piers sees multiple visions of Malvern Hill, including one in which he jousts Jesus. A man in this occupation named Pahom drops dead after taking a bet with the devil in Tolstoy's \"How Much Land does a Man Need?\" Wang Lung begins <em>The Good Earth</em> as poor Chinese peasants in this profession. The human Mr. Jones is in, for the point, what profession in an Orwell story featuring animals like Old Major and Napoleon?", "answer": "<b><u>Farm</u></b>ing (or <b><u>Farm</u></b>er; accept <b><u>Plow</u></b>ing; or <b><u>Plow</u></b>man; accept <b><u>Agriculture</u></b>; prompt on \"Peasant\")", "metadata": "Literature - British Literature - Misc Literature"}, {"question": "A Lotus chalice and meteoric iron dagger were found in this location. This location has a depiction of the \"Opening of the Mouth Ceremony\" with Ay, the predecessor to this location's dedicatee, depicted. Hussein Abdel-Rassoul found a stairway into this location, which Evelyn Herbert visited. Before entering this location with Arthur Callender, an archaeologist said he saw \"Wonderful things!\" Lord Carnarvon died of blood poisoning after entering this location, prompting fears of a curse. Found by Howard Carter, for the point, what is this resting place for an Egyptian boy-pharaoh in the Valley of the Kings?", "answer": "<b><u>KV62</u></b> (accept King <b><u>Tut</u></b>ankhamun's <b><u>Tomb</u></b>; prompt on similar answers to <b><u>tomb</u> </b>such as \"burial place\")", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "A <em>nabob</em> is a European man who rapidly made his fortune by working with this private organization, whose influence led to the trial of their Governor-General Warren Hastings. One of this company's agents named John Zephaniah Holwell wrote an exaggerated account of the imprisonment of soldiers by the Nawab of Bengal in the Black Hole of Calcutta. The Sepoy Mutiny led the government of Great Britain to absorb, for the point, what joint-stock company which controlled much of the Indian subcontinent?", "answer": "<b><u>British East India</u></b> Company (accept <b><u>British EIC</u></b>; accept <b><u>Honourable East India</u> </b>Company; accept <b><u>English East India</u></b> Company; accept <b><u>John Company</u></b>; accept <b><u>Company</u></b> <b><u>Bahadur</u></b>; do not accept or prompt on \"Dutch East India\")", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "During this war, the Caravan War was initiated as part of Operation Curtain and carried about by one side's <em>spetsnaz</em> special forces. A third of the world boycotted the 1980 Moscow Olympics due to the host propping up a government led by Babrak Karmal in this conflict. The CIA supported the mujahedeen in their fight during, for the point, what nine year war which partially caused the collapse of the Soviet Union in the late 1980s?", "answer": "<b><u>Soviet\u2013Afghan</u></b> War (accept <b><u>Soviet Invasion of Afghanistan</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "Helen Keller\u2019s letter against this campaign claimed that certain ideas \u201cpassed through millions of channels and will go on.\u201d An Institute for Sex Research was targeted in this campaign, which was facilitated by the publication of the Twelve Theses, named in of honor of Martin Luther\u2019s similar action involving a papal bull. The term \"S\u00e4uberung\" [ZOY-bare-ung]] or \u201ccleansing\u201d was used to describe this event, which targeted works of such authors as Hesse, Einstein, and Marx. For the point, name this mass destruction of texts by students loyal to Adolf Hitler.", "answer": "<b><u>Nazi Book Burning</u></b>s (accept <b><u>Deutsche Studentenschaft</u></b> or <b><u>DSt</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {"question": "One woman in this city proved her chastity by dragging a large statue of the Great Mother goddess the length of a river. Worshippers in this city threw beans over their shoulders to pacify lemuria ghosts. The Flamen Dialis historically oversaw the sacrifices associated with this city's Lupercalia [[\"LOOPER\"-kal-ee-ah]] festival. Ovid's <em>Metamorphoses</em> ends with the rise of one of this city' rulers to power. This city was founded by a pair of twins who were raised by a she-wolf. For the point, name this city, which once was the center of the worship of Jupiter.", "answer": "<b><u>Rome</u></b> (accept <b><u>Roma</u></b>)", "metadata": "Mythology - Mythology"}, {"question": "Chanakya describes women known as <em>Visha Kanya</em> who used this method to kill political opponents during the era of Chandragupta. First employed as an expert in this field by Agrippina the Younger, a woman named Locusta likely used this method to kill both Claudius and Britannicus to pave the way for Nero's accession. Ancient Egyptians used antimony, arsenic and lead as primary ingredients in make these concoctions. For the point, name these potent chemicals like cyanide used to end one's own or another person's life.", "answer": "<b><u>Poison</u></b>s (accept <b><u>Toxic</u></b>ology; prompt on more general answers like \"Assassination\")", "metadata": "History - Ancient History"}, {"question": "A treatise on this discipline, which begins with the death of Emperor Gratian, has a chapter concerning the layout of temporary settlements known as <em>castrum</em>. In another work in this discipline, the Emperor Maurice outlined an early description of \"Combined Arms\" while writing on the uses of the <em>Tagma</em>. According to a 6th century BCE theorist, all of [this discipline] \"is based on deception.\" Works like <em>Strategikon</em> and another by Sun Tzu describe, for the point, what discipline concerning violent, organized conflicts between entities?", "answer": "<b><u>War</u></b>fare (accept <b><u>Military</u></b> Science; accept answers including Military <b><u>Strategy</u> </b>before mentioned)", "metadata": "Philosophy - Philosophy"}, {"question": "At his trial, this man said that the voice of God sent him on a mission to kill, but he pleaded not guilty on grounds of diminished responsibility. During investigations into this man's crimes, he was interviewed nine times by police before being arrested, leading to the Byford Report criticizing police procedures. This man was convicted of thirteen murders and, while imprisoned in England, began using the name Peter William Coonan. For the point, name this serial killer, dubbed the Yorkshire Ripper by the British press.", "answer": "Peter <b><u>Sutcliffe</u></b> (or Peter William <b><u>Sutcliffe</u></b>; accept <b><u>Yorkshire Ripper</u></b> before mentioned; accept Peter William <b><u>Coonan</u></b> before mentioned)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "This man relied on Vivant Denon [[vee-VANH dee-NONH]] to curate his art collection due to his nearsightedness. Jean-Auguste-Dominique Ingres [[ANGHR]] depicted this leader <em>On His Imperial Throne</em> holding two scepters and wearing a golden laurel wreath. After ordering his troops to take artifacts from Egypt, this leader installed them at the Louvre, which was at the time named after him. For the point, name this French leader, who was depicted at the Saint-Bernard Pass by Jacques-Louis David as he was \"<em>Crossing the</em> <em>Alps</em>.\"", "answer": "<b><u>Napoleon</u></b> Bonaparte (accept <b><u>Napoleon</u></b> I)", "metadata": "Fine Arts - Visual Fine Arts"}, {"question": "This actress played Irene Hoffmann, a German woman who reluctantly testifies at the central tribunal in <em>Judgment at Nuremberg</em>. This woman starred alongside Fred Astaire in <em>Easter Parade</em>. The news of this woman\u2019s 1969 overdose on sleeping pills was allegedly a contributing factor to the Stonewall Riots. The Smithsonian holds a pair of ruby slippers worn by this actress in a movie where she sings \u201cOver the Rainbow.\u201d For the point, name this star of <em>The Wizard of Oz</em>.", "answer": "Judy <b><u>Garland</u></b> (or Frances Ethel <b><u>Gumm</u></b>)", "metadata": "Fine Arts - Other Fine Arts - Film"}, {"question": "Mark Murray reported that this man claimed that the central object used in a 1998 event targeting him \u201cwasn\u2019t even that good.\u201d Noel Godin carried out that attack against this man while he was on his way to speak with E.U. officials in Brussels. This man, who once had a pie thrown in his face, organized his best-known venture with Paul Allen. This businessman founded an organization containing a Global Development Division with his soon-to-be former wife Melinda. For the point, name this founder of Microsoft.", "answer": "Bill <b><u>Gates</u></b> (or William Henry \"Bill\" <b><u>Gates</u></b> III)", "metadata": "Current Events - Current Events"}, {"question": "The most immediate action that brought about this event was organized by Wilhelm Souchon and involved the destruction of the minesweeper <em>Prut</em>. Sergey Sazonov\u2019s refusal to acknowledge another side\u2019s regrets over an attack on the gunboat <em>Donetz</em> instigated this event, which was further precipitated by the Bergmann Offensive. A battle during the Black Sea Raid at Odessa brought about this November 11, 1914 event, in which the central polity called for a jihad. For the point, name this event in which a major Muslim state entered a global conflict.", "answer": "<b><u>Ottoman</u></b> Empire\u2019s <b><u>entry</u></b> into <b><u>World War One</u></b> (accept <b><u>Russia declaring war</u></b> on the <b><u>Ottoman</u></b> Empire during <b><u>World War One</u></b>; prompt on partial answer; prompt on answers involving \u201cTurkey\u201d instead of \u201cOttoman\u201d Empire; accept clear knowledge  equivalents in place of \u201centry\u201d)", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {"question": "When offering a statement regarding his motive for this event, the perpetrator compared his stomach to that of a \u201cdrunk man.\u201d Lilian Cross allegedly struck the perpetrator of this event in the hand. The only fatality in this event allegedly told its target, \"I'm glad it was me, not you.\" Occurring after its target gave a speech at Bayfront Park in Miami, this event resulted in the death of Chicago mayor Anton Cermak. For the point, name this attempt by bricklayer Giuseppe Zangara to kill a New Deal president.", "answer": "<b><u>Attempted assassination</u></b> of <b><u>F</u></b>ranklin Delano <b><u>Roosevelt</u></b> (accept <b><u>FDR</u></b> in place of <b><u>F</u></b>ranklin Delano <b><u>Roosevelt</u></b>; accept clear knowledge equivalents; do not accept or prompt on answers indicating a successful assassination)", "metadata": "History - American History"}], "bonuses": []}